Let's find out how to use Amazon audiences in your Sponsored display campaigns.
Say you're looking to surface your line of sustainably-made coffee makers to eco-conscious
coffee fans.
In your campaign, pick audiences as your targeting strategy.
Then, pick Amazon audiences.
There are four audience segments, lifestyle audiences like green and environmentally conscious,
interests like coffee lovers, life events like recently moved, and in market audiences,
to engage audiences shopping for similar items like pour-over coffee makers.
You can search for
segments or keep clicking to expand them.
Simply click Add to include them in your targeting.